Guide to the Sarah P. Duke Garden Reference Collection, 1934-[ongoing]
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Sarah P. Duke Garden Reference collection 1934-[ongoing]
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. University Archives
1.0 Linear Feet 600 Items
The Sarah P. Duke Gardens Reference Collection contains files of clippings, brochures, maps, history of the gardens, symposium and promotional packets, and other material concerning the Duke Gardens.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Sarah P. Duke Gardens Reference Collection was compiled from a variety of sources by University Archives staff for reference and research.
Collection Overview
The Sarah P. Duke Gardens Reference Collection contains files of clippings, brochures, maps, history of the gardens, symposium and promotional packets, and other material concerning the Duke Gardens.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Durden, Robert Franklin.
Duke University. Sarah P. Duke Gardens.
Duke University. Sarah P. Duke Gardens -- handbooks, manuals, etc.
Duke University. Sarah P. Duke Gardens -- photographs.
Sarah P. Duke Gardens -- History.
Shipman, Ellen.
Related Material
Sarah P. Duke Gardens records. 1932-[ongoing].
University Archives, Duke University.
Contents of Collection
- Container List, 1 Box
  - Annual Report, 2000-2003 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report, 2003-2004
  - Annual Report,2005
  - New Growth, Annual Report, 2006
  - Then and Now, Annual Report, 2007
  - Building Bridges, Annual Report, 2008
  - 75 Years, Annual Report, 2009
  - Printed matter: Campaign to Build the Center for Duke Gardens, 1996
  - Cross References
  - Doris Duke Center
  - Duplicates
  - Durden, Robert F., "Duke Gardens Through the Years," 1997, 2001
  - Event Brochures and Flyers, 1979-
  - Ellen Shipman Symposium, 1998
  - History, 1939-1992
  - Leong, William S. "University Gardens: A Development Plan" 1959 (Box 2)
  - Magazine articles, 1934-1996
  - Printed matter: maps
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973-
  - Shipman, Ellen Biddle
  - Steffek, Edwin Jr. (Horticulturist, Blomquist Garden)